turn down hob
turn on extractor fan
open freezer
open drawer
grab sweet corn
grab carrots
close freezer drawer
close freezer
move lunchbox
grab saucepan
place saucepan
turn on hob
open drawer
grab scissors
close drawer
open carrot bag
pour carrots
open sweet corn
pour sweet corn
grab carrot back
open freezer
open drawer
put carrots
put sweet corn
close drawer
close freezer
grab lid
put lid
shake pan
transfer water
put pan on hob
OPEN DRAWER
GRAB KNIFE
CLOSE DRAWER
CUT POTATOES
GRAB OIL
OPEN OIL
PUT SAUCEPAN ON PAN
POUR OIL
GRAB SPOON
TURN DOWN FAN
MOVE POTATOES
Stir potatoes
Pick up potatoes
Keep stiring potatoes
Shake pan
Stir potatoes
Turn on extractor fan
shake pan
open drawer
grab spoon
close drawer
grab spice
shake pan
stir potatoes
grab pepper
open pepper
grind pepper
close pepper
put pepper
spin spice mix
close spice mix
close spice mix on side
shake pan
stir potatoes
Grab plates
Put plate
Put rubbish in bin
Grab scissors
Open drawer
Put scissors
Close drawer
Grab spoon
Put spoon
Tear off plastic
Tear off paper
Put rubbish in bin
Shake potatoes
Stir potatoes
Turn on water
Wash hands
Grab plastic
Wash plastic
Turn off tap
Put plastic on side
Dry hands
Check potatoes
Stir potatoes
Turn on extractor fan
Turn down hob
Turn off hob
Move saucepan
Put lid on saucepan
Move tap
Drain water
pour vegetables on plate
grab spoon
spoon vegetables
put saucepan
grab saucepan
spoon potatoes
put saucepan on side
turn off oven
open oven
turn off tractor fan
put spoon
grab oven mitts
grab tray
close oven
put tray on side
put down oven mitts
open foil
grab spoon
put on oven mitt
spoon salmon
grab plate
put salmon on plate
put down spoon
grab foil
put foil in bin
put oven mitts on oven
open drawer
grab cutlery
close drawer
[END SUBTITLE]